{"data":[{"question":"They asked me what did happen last night, but I was unable to tell them.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"girls","b":"have","c":"to the","d":"yet","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n\n- Have-> has","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The test administrator ordered we not to open our books until he told us to do so.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"After studying","b":"all the new","c":"was able","d":"rise","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Rise-> raise","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"I would of attended the meeting of the planning committee last week, but I had to deliver a speech at a convention.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"that","b":"see","c":"laying","d":"belongs to","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Laying-> lying","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"We are suppose to read all of chapter seven and answer the questions for tomorrow's class.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"that","b":"goes","c":"to the doctor","d":"returns from","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Goes-> go\nsuggest that somebody do something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The explanation that our instructor gave us was different than the one yours gave you.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"looking","b":"go","c":"finishes","d":"at the","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Go-> going","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"In the sixteenth century, Spain became involved in foreign wars with several other European countries and could not find the means of finance the battles that ensued.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"that","b":"jumped","c":"of","d":"plunged into","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Of-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Neither of the girls have turned in the term papers to the instructor yet.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"jogging","b":"crisp morning","c":"during","d":"the winter months","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Jogging-> jog","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"After studying all the new materials, the student was able to rise his test score by twenty-five points.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"first","b":"success","c":"was designed","d":"German","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Success-> successful","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The book that you see laying on the table belongs to the teacher.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"could he have","b":"gone","c":"so early","d":"in the","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Could he have gone-> he could have gone","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"I suggest that he goes to the doctor as soon as he returns from talking the exam.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of defending","b":"their","c":"forced","d":"to retreat","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Of defending-> to defend","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"}]}